Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records Concerning Community Relations
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records concerning community relations, 1969-1986; Accession 1987-A-114
  - Studies, Miscellaneous
    - City of New Haven Office of Policy Analysis, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 439)
    - Columbus-Battelle Proposal, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 440)
    - Regionalism, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 441)
  - Sulfur, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 442)
  - Summer Crisis Committee, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 443)
  - Summer and Special Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 444)
  - Summer and Special Programs Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 445)
  - Summer Day Camp at Yale, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 446)
  - Task Force Analysis
    - 1977 (Box 30, Folder 447)
    - Completed, 1977 Fall (Box 30, Folder 448)
    - Completed, 1978 Spring (Box 30, Folder 449)
    - Final Questionnaire, undated (Box 30, Folder 450)
  - Taxes
    - Legislation, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 451)
    - Stalberg Data, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 452)
    - 1979 (Box 30, Folder 453)
    - 1972-1981 (Box 30, Folder 454)
    - 1972-1981 (Box 31, Folder 455)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 456)
  - Taxable Lists, 1977-1980 (Box 31, Folder 457)
  - Time-Life Books, 1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 458)
  - Town-Gown
    - Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 459)
    - Column, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 460)
    - Committee, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 461)
    - Tours, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 462)
  - Tweed Airport, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 463)
  - Umoja Extended Family, 1973-1980 (Box 31, Folder 464)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 465)
  - Undergraduate Schools Committee, New Haven, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 466)
  - Unions
    - Union Strike: Local 35 (Box 31, Folder 467)
    - C and T Union, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 468 - 470)
  - United Way
    - Campaign, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 471)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 32, Folder 472)
    - 1977 (Box 32, Folder 473)
    - Planning Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 474)
  - University Stationary, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 475)
  - Upward Bound, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 476)
  - Urban Development Action Group, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 477)
  - Urban League, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 478)
  - Urban Reinvestment Opportunities Program, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 479)
  - Urban Universities Meeting (Box 33, Folder 480)
  - Urban Improvement Corps (Box 33, Folder 481)
  - Vandalism, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 482)
  - Visitors, 1980-1983 (Box 33, Folder 483)
  - Warren, David, 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 484)
  - WELI, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 485)
  - Western Perimeter, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 486)
  - White Collar Unionizing, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 487)
  - Whitney Grove, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 488 - 489)
  - Whitney Grove, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 490 - 491)
  - Woolsey Hall
    - 1983 (Box 34, Folder 493)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 494)
  - Work Study Program
    - Off-Campus Work Study, 1979-1984 (Box 34, Folder 495)
    - Evaluations, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 496)
    - Off-Campus, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 497)
  - World Wildlife Animal Exhibit, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 498)
  - WTNH-TV, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 499)
  - Yale Charities Drive, 1974-1984 (Box 34, Folder 500)
  - Yale Charter, 1975-1981 (Box 34, Folder 501)
  - Yale Club of New Haven, 1974-1981 (Box 35, Folder 502)
  - Yale College: Zeta Psi Fraternity, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 503)
  - Yale Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 504)
  - Yale Corporation Advisory Committee On Governmental Affairs, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 505)
  - Yale Enterprises, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 506)
  - Yale Gift Horse, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 507)
  - Yale Graduate Students, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 508)
  - Yale-New Haven Contest, undated (Box 35, Folder 509)
  - Yale New Haven Teachers Institute
    - General, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 510 - 512)
    - 1980-1984 (Box 35, Folder 513 - 514)
    - 1980-1984 (Box 36, Folder 515)
  - Yale-State of Connecticut Relations, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 516)
  - Yale University Police Force, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 517)
  - Yale Volunteer Service, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 518)
  - Youth Assistance Group, 1974-1978 (Box 36, Folder 519)
  - RESTRICTED
    - Admissions and Applications, 1977-1983 (Box 37, Folder 520 - 521)
    - Athletics-Confidential, Football Passes, 1980- (Box 37, Folder 522)
    - Athletics-Confidential, Football Passes, 1975-1979 (Box 37, Folder 523)
    - Compensation and Reimbursement Sheets, 1981-1983 (Box 37, Folder 524)
- Records concerning community and state relations, 1915-1986; Accession 1990-A-049
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  - Mellon Foundation, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New Haven Delegation to General Assembly, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New Haven Economic Development Commission (NHEDC), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New Haven Office of Downtown Development, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - New Haven Wards, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New Haven Foundation Seminar, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Olin, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Onorato, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Oranoque Forest, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Physicians Assistants -Legislation, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Parking Violations, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Privacy -Bills, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Public Acts -1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Public Acts -1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Regional Council on Education (RCEE), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Reagan -Education Budget, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Receptions, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Retirement -1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Retirement Legislation in Connecticut-Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Retirement, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Save Our Schools, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Schnellen -Senator, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Science Park Development Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Security -Yale, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Senior Citizens Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sewers (5 files), 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 27-31)
  - Sewers -Industrial Waste Charge, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Shubert Theater, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Smoke Detection, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Spanish for Medical Personnel, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - State of Connecticut -Department of Education, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - State Relations, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Stolberg Bill No. 5959 (2 files), 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
  - Sulfur Release, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sulfur -Legislation, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sulfur -Background Information, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Sulfur, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Taxation -Athletic Properties, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Sulfur -Variance, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Sulfur -1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Symposium -State and Local Government, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - New Haven Transportation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Yale Taxation, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Taxation -Federal Legislation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Teacher Preparation, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Ted's Seminar, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Toxics, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Town -Group Clips, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Underwriter's Laboratory, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Unions, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - University of Bridgeport -State Related, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Washington Updates, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Sulfur Articles, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Interns, 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - T.P. Stevens, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Surveys, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Mayor's Portraits, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Mayor's Task Force, 1976-78 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Cancer Center -Cedar St. Bridge, 1974-78 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - New Career for Women, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Women -Career Directions, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Non-Yale Use of Facilities, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Viennese New Year's Eve, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Downtown Places Tour, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Women -Employment Resource Center, Inc., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Water Pollution Control Authority, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Yale -Agency Accounts, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Yale Arts, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Yale -Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Yale -Business, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Yale Charter -Enfranchisement of Recent Graduates, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Yale College Council, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Yale College Seminars., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Yale Information Group, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Yale Legislative Services, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Yale -New Haven Hospital, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Yale -New Haven Hospital: Air Rights Garage, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Yale -New Haven, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Yale -New Haven: Initiatives, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Yale -New Haven: Newborns, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Yale -New Haven: Teachers Institute, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Yale Charter -Revision, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Tweed New Haven Airport, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Yale Student Policies, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Yale -State Initiatives, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Yale Enterprises, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Route 34, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Title IX, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Department of Higher Education, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - State Contracting -Independent Colleges, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 96a)
  - Meeting with New Haven Alderman, City Administration, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - New Haven Board of Aldermen Meetings, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Governor's Committee on Fitness, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Comprehensive Youth Program (CYP), 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - CYP Meetings
    - 1986 Mar 24 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - 1985 Jan 22 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - 1985 Nov 4 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - 1985 Oct 7 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Comprehensive Youth Logo, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - CYP Brochure, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - CYP Meeting: Aug 5, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - CYP: Agendas, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - CYP: Non-Public Agencies, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - CYP Meeting: Aug 14, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - GYP Marketing, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - GYP Budget, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - CYP Committee, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Recreation Advisory Council, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - GYP, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - CYP, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Youth Program: News Release and Surveys, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - School Surveys, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - New Haven/Yale -Community Service Programs, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - New Haven/Yale -Tax Discussions of July, August, September, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Whitney-Grove Residential Colleges
    - Names, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Havemeyer House, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Parking, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Construction Schedule, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Commercial Space, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - October 1971 -June 1972 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - July 1972 -October 1972 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - November 1972 -December 1972 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Summary of Discussions, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Publicity, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - New Haven/Yale -Economic Development, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Whitney-Grove Residential Colleges Jan. -Feb., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - New Haven/Yale -Community Relations, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - New Haven/Yale -Tax Discussions Publicity, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Residential Colleges: Alternative Housing Committee, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Residential Colleges: Alternative Housing Prospect Holiday Inn, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Residential Colleges: Alternative Housing Prospects Declined, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - New Haven/Yale: Tax Discussions Trustees Meeting, September 15 1972 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - New Haven/Yale: Yale Council on Community Affairs, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Whitney-Grove Residential College: Security, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Paul Mellon Center for British Art and British Studies: Prospective Tenants, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Whitney-Grove Residential College, 26724 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Harvard and Tax Exemption, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Report of the Joint Study Group on Legal and Economic Relations Between Universities and their Host Communities, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Tax Exempt Property Study Commission Report October, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Temporary Residence Tax (Bed Tax") Rokoff Paper ", 1972 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Ranney Report: University Counsel Commission on Community Relations, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Whitney-Grove: Spare Copies of Relevant Material, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - DeVane Lectures, Fall, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Trades, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Tent: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Uptown Council, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Urban Futures: Spring 1984 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Urban Futures: Fall 1985 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Work Study, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Work Study Evaluation Forms, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Communiversity Day, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Publicity: Communiversity Day, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Communiversity, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Recruiting Participants, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Finances, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Publicity, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Communiversity, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Communiversity, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Publicity: Communiversity, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Communiversity, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Recuiring Participants, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Communiversity: Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Communiversity: Community Relations, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Communiversity: Booths, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Communiversity: Publicity, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Communiversity: Entertainment, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Projects/Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Staff Meetings -R, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Items of Interest, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Connecticut Recreation in State Parks and Forests, undated (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Dixwell Community House, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Essex Steamtrain, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Liberty Belle Cruises, undated (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - The New Haven Colony Historical Society, undated (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - New Haven, City IIGateway to New England, undated (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - New Haven Harbor, undated (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - New Haven: Shopping Guide, undated (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - New Haven: The Best Place To Be General Facts/Location, undated (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Student Liaison From Residential Colleges, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Liaison: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Liaisons: Activities, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Pardee-Morris House, New Haven Connecticut, undated (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Self-Guided Walking Tour Fort Nathan Hale, undated (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Steamtrain and Riverboat Guide, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - The Sound Research Program, undated (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Thanksgiving Vacation Guide to New Haven, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Upper State Street, undated (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Asians at Yale, undated (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - A Guide to-Walking Tour of Yale University (Spanish and English), undated (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Libraries at Yale, undated (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - Map of Buildings, undated (Box 4, Folder 202)
  - Whitney Humanities Center Yale University, undated (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - Yale Center for the British Art, undated (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - Yale Memorial Carillon, undated (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - Yale Peabody Museum, undated (Box 4, Folder 206)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, undated (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Adult Literacy Volunteers, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - Higher Education, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - New Haven Public Schools, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - Instruments Transplant, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 211)
  - Honors Dinner, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - High School Students and Yale, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - School Volunteers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - Public School Art Exhibit, undated (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - Mecha/AASA, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - CASA Cultural J. de B., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - Afro-American House, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - State Street Trip, December 7, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - Branford Coffee House, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 221)
  - Liaisons: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - Spring Break/SAC IIGuide to New Haven, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 223)
  - Liaisons: Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 224)
  - Liaisons: Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 225)
  - Spring Vacation Guide to New Haven, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 226)
  - Bus Tour for Liaisons, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 227)
  - Community Liaison Committee: Extra Copies, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 228)
  - Community Liaison Committee ,Agendas and Minutes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 229)
  - Holiday Shopping Trip, December 6, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 230)
  - Community Liaison Committee Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 231)
  - Community Liaison Committee: Projects, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 232)
  - Community Liaison Committee: Newsletter/Tab1etents, undated (Box 5, Folder 233)
  - Community Liaisons: Evaluations, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 234)
  - Liaison Reception, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 235)
  - Community Liaison Committee: General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - Liaison Tour, October 24, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Freshman/Graduate Bus Tour, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - Bus Tour for PROP Students and Panel Discussion Pre-Registration Orientation Program, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - PROP Freshman Counselors Bus Tour, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - Bus Tours for Freshman and Families, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - Department of Higher Education State of Connecitcut, f987 (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - Connecticut College Research Funding Survey, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - Miscellaneous Higher Education, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (C.C.I.C.), 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 245-247)
  - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges Viewbook, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 248)
  - Fall Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 249)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - Norwich Meeting, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 251)
  - Board of Governors for Higher Education, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 252-254)
  - Communiversity Day
    - Finances, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - Publicity, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - Activities and Entertainment, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - W.B.and C. Computer List, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - New Haven Demgraphies, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - Public Schools: Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Alliance Theater, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Alliance Publicity material, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Black Music at the Movies" Yale Art Gallery: Janet 'Gordon ", undated (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Business Day at Yale, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - Graduate/Professional: Town/Gown Relations Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Graduate/Professional: Student Open House, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - AIDS Task Force at Yale, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - Teenage Pregnancy, Infant Mortality, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - Yale Arts Collection, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 270)
  - Faces and Places: New Haven": Public Schools Art Exhibit ", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 271)
  - Black Music at the Movies, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - Community Relations: Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 273)
  - Council on Priorities and Planning Report, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - Council on Priorities and Planning: Cultural Interaction, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - Foreman Report, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - Poverty Commission Report, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 277-288)
  - Musical Events, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - Calendar of Events, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - Events Information Recieved, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - List: Survey contacts and Procedures, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - Elderly Services: Annual Report, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - Shuttle Bus, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - Employee Volunteer Newsletter and Program, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 286-287)
  - Freshman Bazaar, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 288-289)
  - Eating Disorders, Council on, undated (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center (AACC) and Coalition of 100 Black Women Arts Fair, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - Staff meeting and Project up-dates, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - Contacts and Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - Mailing Labels, undated (Box 6, Folder 294)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - Elm-Ivy Awards, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 296)
  - Goodwin-Levine Adult Day, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - Miscellaneous Projects, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 298)
  - Dixwell Q House, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - Brainstorming Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - Calendar of Events, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - Arts Council Day at Yale, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - Advisory Committee: Yale Volunteer Services, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - New Haven Public Schools, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - Yale/New Haven Teachers' Institute, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - Work-Study and Volunteer Options, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Walk Against Hunger, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - United Illuminating and Afro-American Cultural Center High School Trip, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - Public Service Careers Day, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - Promoting Neighborhood Recovery in. New Haven, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - Leadership and Organization, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - Ivy Group Conference, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - A Promotions Guide to Commercial Revitalization, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - Andriette (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Blank Calendars, undated (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - City of New Haven Organization Chart, undated (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - City of New Haven Student Volunteer Forms, undated (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Committee Bill Record, undated (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Enjoying New Haven: Update, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Index of Organizations by Catagory, undated (Box 6, Folder 321)
  - Legislative Alert, undated (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - List of Community Organizations, undated (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - New Haven Bike Rides, undated (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - New Haven Convention and Visitors Bureau: Guide to New Haven, undated (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - New Haven Landmarks, undated (Box 6, Folder 326)
  - New Haven Running Routes, undated (Box 6, Folder 327)
  - Park Ranger Review (New Haven), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 328)
  - A Partial List of Non-Yale Use of Facilities, undated (Box 6, Folder 329)
  - Policies for Use of Yale Facilities, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 330)
  - Procedures for Graduate Students for Work-Study, undated (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - Purchase Requisitions, undated (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - Remittance Slips, undated (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - Request for Services (lacking), undated (Box 6, Folder 334)
  - Student Intern Form, undated (Box 6, Folder 335)
  - Work-Study Opportunities (non-social service), undated (Box 6, Folder 336)
  - Work-Study Programs: Student Guidelines, undated (Box 6, Folder 337)
  - Yale University Fact Sheet, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 338)
  - Upper State St. Trip -Dec, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - Value of local business inventory committed to college-related business #20 -Sep, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 340)